hangerproject.com 2013-09-25

# Our Privacy Policy : Men's Suit Hangers : Wood Hangers : Kirby Allison’s Hanger Project

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

\- To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

\- To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**McAfee Secure Site Monitoring**

We utilize [McAfee Secure](https://www.mcafeesecure.com/RatingVerify?ref=hangerproject.com) site monitoring to scan our website daily for thousands of hacker vulnerabilities in order to maintain the highest level of site security.

**Advanced SSL Browsing Environment**

We use [Symantec's Secure Site Pro with Extended Validation](https://www.symantec.com/verisign/ssl-certificates/secure-site-pro-ev), the most advanced SSL Certificate available, during checkout in order to guarantee the highest level of encryption available on the internet. Any personal information entered during checkout will be transmitted over the internet using a minimum 128-bit encryption. Furthermore, Norton provides an additional daily scan of our website against threats and Malware.

**Additional Malware Scanning**

In addition to McAfee and Symantec / Norton, we utilize a daily malware service provided by [Sucuri](http://sucuri.net/services/web-integrity-monitoring) to guard against malware attacks on our website.

**PayPal is our Merchant Processor**

All Credit Card payments are processed through PayPal, which serves as our merchant processor. We do not store or process credit card information on any of our own servers. All credit card information is passec securely to and processed by PayPal. We use PayPal as our Merchant Processor because they offer some of the highest security on the internet.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on October 30, 2012

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

3000 West Commerce Street, Ste. 116  
Dallas, Texas 75212  
United States of America  
(800) 495-3201
